First up, less is more.
Savings.
Pay attention to what you're spending and cut back where you can.
Track your spending over a couple of months.
You'll probably be surprised where your money is going.
Limit eating out.
All those lattes take out dinners on the Go Protein Chakes.
Many people find that they spend a large chunk of their income on eating out.
Set a limit for yourself and stick to it.
You should also try to limit impulse purchases.
They can be a killer for your savings.
But it's just so easy.
It is.
But tapping your way to happiness now may make you stressed in the future.
Think through what you buy.
Make sure you need those new shoes or jeans.
And don't forget all those subscription services.
Are you really watching Netflix Prime and HBO?
How many shows can you really binge at once?
You can always pause the subscription and pick it back up when you're ready.
It's all about balance.
Use some money to make you happy now and save some to enjoy later.
Number two.